Rent is a music, tv movie, drama film directed by Alex Rudzinski.
The story of several friends in New York City facing financial
poverty, homophobia, AIDS, and, of course, rent.
Mark Cohen, played by Jordan Fisher.
Roger Davis, played by Brennin Hunt.
Maureen Johnson, played by Vanessa Hudgens.
Joanne Jefferson, played by Kiersey Clemons.
Tom Collins, played by Brandon Victor Dixon.
Angel Dumont Schunard, played by Valentina.
Room for Rent is a 2019 mystery-horror film written by Stuart Flack,
directed by Tommy Stovall and starring Lin Shaye.
The movie was produced by Pasidg Productions Inc.
and distributed by Uncork'd Entertainment.
Room for Rent was released on February 23, 2019, at the Sedona
International Film Festival in Sedona, Arizona.
The film concerns an aging widow who rents a room in
her house in order to make some money.
Things take a deadly turn when she becomes strangely
obsessed with one of her new tenants.
The film explores themes of new york city, aids,
musical, based on play or musical, remake.
The tone is emotional.